https://www.ascouncil.org/page/privacy_policy?

ASC Privacy Policy - Adhesive and Sealant Council
Search »
Contact Us   |   Sign In   |   Create an account
Membership
Join NowMEMBER BENEFITSMEMBER CATEGORIESMember CompaniesFAQsAdhesives.org
ABOUT
Coronavirus Resource CenterCrisis Recovery ProgramMission and VisionInnovation Awards ProgramASC Scholarship ProgramBoard of DirectorsCommittees
Global Resources CommitteeRegulatory Affairs CommitteeMembership CommitteeMARKETING COMMITTEETECHNICAL COMMITTEE
MEMBER COMPANIESASC BylawsStandardsSustainabilityContact UsPrivacy Policy
Events
Upcoming ASC EventsVirtual Annual ConventionVirtual Annual EXPOVirtual Adhesive Science Short CourseWebinarsAbstract Submission (Convention)Virtual Additives Short CourseAbstract Submission (WAC2021)Other Events
Education
Training Academy OverviewTechnical ProgramB2B Business ProgramLeadership ProgramCertificate Program Overview
Career CenterNewsStore
On Demand WebinarsFree Friday Webinars (on demand)ITR Market Forecasting ToolCertificate ProgramPast Proceedings
ConventionsShort Courses
Industry ReportsAdvertise
Advocacy
Regulatory IssuesRegulatory ToolkitU.S. VOC RegulationsRegulatory Workshops (Videos)Action CenterLinks
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
ASC Privacy Policy
Share
|
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: May 24, 2018
The Adhesive and Sealant Council, Inc. (ASC) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting the information you provide to us. The information below summarizes our privacy policy.
Information ASC Collects
Mailing Lists
ASC collects and utilizes different kinds of information voluntarily disclosed to ASC either online or in writing through publication order forms, meeting registration forms, surveys, and relevant emails to enable the processing of the order or registration. This information usually includes your name, title, mailing address, phone number and/or email address.
We use personal information provided to improve the services we offer. This information is kept confidential by ASC and is used for internal purposes. We do not sell our email lists to third parties.
We use a third party provider, YourMembership, to deliver our bulk email communications. We gather statistics on email open rates using industry standards to help us monitor engagement with those to whom we email and improve our communications. For more information please see https://www.ascouncil.org/ams/legal-privacy.htm.
ASC Training Academy-related bulk emails are sent to members and customers via third party provider LogMeIn. Their privacy policy may be found here: https://www.logmeininc.com/legal/overview.
ASC utilizes SurveyMonkey to conduct surveys, such as to gauge attendee satisfaction with ASC events, as well as membership ballots, such as to vote on ASC Board candidates and bylaw changes. Their privacy policy may be found here: https://www.surveymonkey.com/mp/legal/privacy-policy/?ut_source=footer.
Opt Out
You may opt out of receiving additional communications from ASC by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our email communications or by emailing privacy@ascouncil.org to have your name removed from our lists. You may also contact us at 301.986.9700 or write to us at 7101 Wisconsin Avenue, Suite 990, Bethesda, MD 20814.
Credit Cards
ASC does not disclose credit card account information provided by our members or customers other than to credit card processors to process your purchase orders, registration, or donations. If you pay for registrations and/or products with a credit card, we collect your credit card number (employing industry standard security and encryption technologies), billing information and e-mail address to process your payment.
How ASC Uses Your Information
We use the information mentioned above in a number of ways, such as:
•	Processing purchase transactions, meeting registrations, and donations;
•	Periodic marketing messages;
•	Verifying your identity, such as when using ASC’s Members-Only portions of our website;
•	Responding to your requests and communicating with you;
•	Performing analytics from surveys on the quality of ASC programs and events;
•	Tallying ballot responses; and/or
•	Complying with applicable legal requirements.
What ASC Discloses to Others
ASC may share the information we collect from and about you within our organization and with certain vendors or partners with whom ASC has a contractual relationship. For example, we may share your information with:
•	Credit card processors to process your payment, registration, or donation;
•	Other ASC websites, such as adhesives.org/sealants.org; and/or
•	Other organizations with whom we work to create the ASC EXPO and our other events.
We hold our vendors and partners to the same high level of data privacy standards that we use internally. ASC never sells your personal information to any organization, and our vendors and partners are required to hold your information confidential and for ASC-contracted purposes only.
Updating Your Information
You are entitled to change or update your personal information at any time by logging into ascouncil.org (https://www.ascouncil.org/login.aspx), emailing privacy@ascouncil.org, or contacting us at the telephone number or address above for assistance.
Updates to ASC’s Privacy Policy
We may periodically update the privacy policy and post the revised version on this page with “last updated” listed. Changes will become effective immediately.
Sign In
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Don't have an account?
Latest News
more
10/8/2020Post Covid-19 Polymers’ Point to a Antimicrobial Future Full of Solutions10/6/2020Flame Retardant Thermoplastics Polyester Web Adhesive Sandwich Panels Speeds Aerospace Production
Calendar
more
10/16/2020FF: Instron's New Universal Testing Systems – Simpler, Smarter, Safer than Ever Before10/29/2020Facility Operations during COVID-19: Guidelines for Protecting Worker Health & Safety & Case Study
Visit our end user portal at:
© 2012 The Adhesive and Sealant Council | 510 King Street, Suite 418 | Alexandria, Virginia 22314
Phone: (301) 986-9700 | Fax: (301) 986-9795
Privacy Policy
Membership Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
